Matthew George Mungall

07547944806 East Kilbride, Glasgow

matthewmungall96@gmail.com

Software Developer / Games Programmer

GitHub: matthewmungall96 LinkedIn: Matthew-Mungall

I am a first-class games development honours graduate with one years' experience in the software industry, with experience working with both computer application and mobile game development in both industry and education-based fields. I have been interested in programming from a young age, eventually finding myself applying to further education in the field of software development.

I am a motivated, committed and driven individual, who always enjoys the problem solving aspect regarding the software industry. Thank you for taking the time to look at my CV.

SKILLS

Tools and Languages Programmes

C#, C++, SQL, PHP, HTML/CSS, Git, CMD

Unity, Unreal, Visual Studio, Blender, Office, MySQL, GitHub Desktop, SourceTree, Android Studio

WORK EXPERIENCE

Specialist Programmer

02/2021- 08/2021

Poly Fruit Studios LTD London, England (Contract)

- Utilised prototyping for numerous hyper casual pitches in a team-based setting, where I continued to hone my C# programming skills.
- Assisted Lead Programmers with recruiting new programmers for the company.
- Managed a team for Tools Development for development inside of the company.
- · Evaluated my team's work with our producer, and reacted to feedback accordingly.

UI Programmer

06 2020-02 2021

London, England (Contract)

Poly Fruit Studios LTD
 Used C# to write, maintain and refactor code for the studio's first developed title, Kingdom Jump.

- Worked with Git and GitHub Desktop to push, pull and fix conflicts on the company's repository.
- Worked with Git and GitHub Desktop to push, putt and fix conflicts on the company's repository.
 Communicated with artists daily to implement their designs via social platforms such as Discord and Google Chat.
- Managed a team of up to ten recent university graduates at a time via stand-up meetings and utilising Agile/Kanban methodologies.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Games Development (First Class)

2017-2020

University West of Scotland (Lanarkshire)

Hamilton, Scotland

- Learned the principles of Computer Games Design and Development.
- · Worked in team based environments to emulate the games development process to an industry standard.
- Learned how to create game applications through Unity, Phaser and Unreal game engines.
- Improved my proficiency with using C#, SQL, HTML/CSS and JavaScript.
- Created multiple games applications to a high standard, with supporting written and video documentation.
- Achieved a score of 90 percent in my Dissertation Project, which focused on the implementation of Games Based Learning and the development of a games application to support this theory.

Higher National Diploma in Software Development

2015-2017

Glasgow Clyde College (Langside Campus)

Glasgow, Scotland

- Introduced to concepts such as Object-Orientated Programming, Databases, Human Computer Interfaces and Data Structures.
- Learned new programming languages (SQL, PHP and C++) while also gaining knowledge on the Linux System and MySQL Database.
- While completing my HND, I also completed a Oracle course regarding SQL Relational Databases, which resulted in achieving a
 certificate.
- Created a PHP, HTML and SQL based system to deal with tracking patients in the NHS, which resulted in me getting an A grade for my HND.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Completed the UK Government's Kick Start Scheme via Work Placement Obtained my Driving License Developed multiple games based applications in my free time Achieved an Oracle Certificate in SQL Relational Databases 2021

Nov 2018

2017-present

Jun 2017